I'm Christina Koch,
I'm a mission specialist
on the Artemis II mission to the moon.
When I first found out that I was assigned
to Artemis II, my thoughts were disbelief,
an immense sense of honor
and responsibility,
and readiness.
I'm ready to try to make everyone proud
and to really fulfill what this
mission truly means to all humanity.
For me, there's never really been a time
when I didn't want to be an astronaut.
Going back, as far as I can remember,
it's what I always dreamed of.
I think the spark was really lit
when I visited Kennedy Space Center
with my family and came home
with a bunch of posters that then went up
on the walls of my bedroom and became
the things that I dreamed of from then on.
When I think about the Artemis II crew,
my first thought is that I am
so privileged to be a part of it.
These other astronauts
have an amazing history,
amazing record, amazing experience,
and they're great people.
I've known them all for many, many years.
I've had a chance to work
with them in different capacities,
and I think our skills
really complement each other.
They all have a military background,
and I come from a more raw,
technical engineering background,
and I think that that complements
one another really well.
I think we'll work together great,
and I hope to be someone on the crew
that really is that engineering expert,
and I hope that that can be the way
that I contribute the most.